perfectplaces.com 2017-03-31

# Perfect Places Privacy Notice | PerfectPlaces.com

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

PerfectPlaces.com, forGetaway.com, RentJillsHouse.com, LakeRentals.com, and CoastRentals.com are all websites owned and operated by Perfect Places. Perfect Places respects the privacy of every individual who visits our web sites, responds to our interactive advertisements or purchases goods and/or services. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. This Privacy Statement outlines the information Perfect Places will collect and how that information will be used. This Statement will also instruct you on what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or further disseminated.

**The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Perfect Places websites.

Inquiry Information:  
On property listing pages, you have the option of sending email inquiries directly to the property owner or manager. Email sent through the "Email Your Inquiry" links found on property listings are sent directly to the property advertiser. If you choose to send an inquiry using these links, your personal information, including your email address and any other information you supply, will be emailed to the advertiser whose property you inquired about. The property advertisers will generally reply directly to you. Do not share information in the email that you do not want property advertisers to see. The types of personal information collected when submitting an inquiry are: 

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Travel Dates
  * Number of in Party

Online Reservation Information:  
On certain property listing pages, you have the option of making an online reservation. Online reservations are sent directly to the property advertiser. If you choose to make an online reservation, your personal information, including your name, email address, credit card and any other information you supply, will be securely transferred to the advertiser whose property you reserved. The property advertisers will generally reply directly to you. Do not share information in the online reservation that you do not want property advertisers to see. The types of personal information collected when submitting an online reservation are: 

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Travel Dates
  * Number of in Party
  * Credit Card Information

Email to a Friend Information:  
On property listing pages, you have have the option of sending email summaries of properties to another person by using the "Email to a Friend" link. Do not share information in the email that you do not want the receiving party you specify to see. The types of personal information collected when sending an email to friend are: 

  * Name
  * Email address

Registered Customer Information:  
If you are listing your property, personal information you provide to the company will be used to identify you as a customer of the company and to provide payment. The types of personal information collected for registered customers are: 

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email addresses
  * Phone numbers
  * Credit Card Information

Non-Personally-Identifiable Information Collected Automatically  
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the web site from which you linked to our site or advertisement. 

**The Way We Use Information**  

Inquiry Information:  
Perfect Places stores a copy of inquiries as a record for advertisers and will add your email address to its mailing list. The mailing list is used exclusively by Perfect Places for newsletters and notification of special offers. Perfect Places mailing list is not given or sold to any third party. You may remove your email address from our mailing list at any time by entering your email address at our unsubscribe page. 

Online Reservation Information:  
Perfect Places stores a copy of online reservations as a record for advertisers and will add your email address to its mailing list. The mailing list is used exclusively by Perfect Places for newsletters and notification of special offers. Perfect Places mailing list is not given or sold to any third party. You may remove your email address from our mailing list at any time by entering your email address at our unsubscribe page. 

Email to a Friend Information:  
Perfect Places stores a copy of email to a friend requests as a record and will add your email address to its mailing list. The mailing list is used exclusively by Perfect Places for newsletters and notification of special offers. Perfect Places mailing list is not given or sold to any third party. You may remove your email address from our mailing list at any time by entering your email address at our unsubscribe page. 

Registered Customer Information:  
For registered customers who list properties with Perfect Places, personal information you provide to the company will be used to identify you as a customer of the company and in connection with delivering services or products that you order. Personal financial information will also be obtained to secure payment. By providing personal information for these purposes you agree to be placed on marketing lists and may receive promotional notices from the company. Personal information may also be gathered from you to assist with marketing programs designed to identify broad market groups for specific promotional opportunities.

Non-Personally-Identifiable Information Collected Automatically  
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our websites and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser or registered customer that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our websites, or that X number of people visited from Y country, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your personal information, Perfect Places cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our websites from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our websites is structured to attract anyone under 18. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**  

Inquiry Information:  
You may remove your email address provided on the Email Your Inquiry page from our mailing list at any time by entering your email address at our unsubscribe page. 

Online Reservation Information:  
You may remove your email address provided on the Online Reservation pages from our mailing list at any time by entering your email address at our unsubscribe page. 

Email to a Friend Information:  
You may remove your email address provided on the on the Email To a Friend page from our mailing list at any time by entering your email address at our unsubscribe page. 

Registered Customer Information:  
Registered customer can modify or remove their personal information at any time using the forms provided in the Owner/Manager tools. If you are a registered customer and wish to modify or remove your information, please log in using the following link (<https://www.perfectplaces.com/tools/>) or clicking on the "Log-In" link at the top of any page. You can also have us make changes to your information on your behalf by sending us a request. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [ customerservice@perfectplaces.com](mailto:customerservice@perfectplaces.com). 

revised: December 5, 2014
